A Guide to the Records of the University Club, 1925-2000
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Records of the University Club, 1925-2000
Special Collections, Virginia Tech, Blacksburg, Va.
RG 29/4
13.6 Cubic Feet; 9 boxes and 1 oversized folder
The collection consists of papers detailing the founding, construction, administration, finances, and membership of the University Club at Virginia Tech.
Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University. University Club (1925-)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Acquisition Information
The Records of the University Club was donated to Special Collections in May 2006.
Administrative History
A Virginia Tech faculty group organized the University Club in 1925. The clubhouse, formerly located on Otey Street, was built on land leased from the university. In June 1929, construction began on the clubhouse. Soon the club gained 125 members and has continued to grow throughout the years. It was completed in 1930 at a cost of $38,000. It contains 8,773 square feet. It once contained a dining room, which ceased operations in 1935 when the old Faculty Center dining room opened. On December 2, 1953 at the annual meeting members burned the last of the bonds representing the indebtedness of $40,000 incurred in building the clubhouse on campus. The building was valued at $70,000 in 1953. The Virginia Tech Foundation purchased the clubhouse in December 2017, and it was demolished the following year.
Since the founding, the membership has included Nobel Prize winners, University Presidents, corporate and civic leaders, and distinguished artists and professors. The club's mission is to "provide programs to enhance the cultural and social life of its members and maintain a suitable clubhouse."
Scope and Content
The collection consists of papers detailing the founding, construction, administration, finances, and membership of the University Club at Virginia Tech.
Series I includes meeting minutes and history. The second series comprises contracts, certificates, and the club constitution. Administrative correspondence makes up the third series. Series IV is comprised of account books as well as credit and payment books. Budget material can be found in Series V. Financial records constitute the sixth series. Tax information is located in Series VII. Workbooks are included in the eighth series. Management records are organized in the ninth series. Series X stores operational records. Construction records are filed in Series XI. Series XII contains community and outreach records. Fundraising material is situated in Series XIII. Personal correspondence and images can be found in the fourteenth series. The fifteenth series includes guest books. Membership operations material is located in Series XVI. Series XVII contains registers. Series XVIII contains Residence and Use material. Social events records are filed in the nineteenth series, and Series XX is made up of Steinway Piano material.
Arrangement
The records are arranged into series by the type of material. Within each series, materials are arranged chronologically. Box 4-Folder 39 and Box 9-Folder 1 have been moved to Oversize Folder 1.
Series I: Board of Directors, Minutes, and History, 1929-1999
Series II: Contracts, Certificates, and Constitution, 1925-1986
Series III: Administrative Correspondence, 1930-1991
Series IV: Account Books & Credit and Payment Books, 1926-1978
Series V: Budget, 1986-1999
Series VI: Financial Records, 1929-1999
Series VII: Taxes, 1989-1999
Series VIII: Workbooks, 1952-1957
Series IX: Management, 1980-1999
Series X: Operations, 1984-1999
Series XI: Construction, 1927-1998
Series XII: Community and Outreach, 1965-2000
Series XIII: Fundraising, 1983-1998
Series XIV: Personal Correspondence and Images, 1956
Series XV: Guest Books, 1982-1987
Series XVI: Membership Operations, 1974-1999
Series XVII: Registers, 1984-1998
Series XVIII: Residence and Use, 1957-1998
Series XIX: Social Events, 1981-2000
Series XX: Steinway Piano, 1989-1991
Index Terms
Subjects:
University Archives; University History
Organizations:
Virginia Agricultural and Mechanical College and Polytechnic Institute; Virginia Polytechnic Institute; Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University; Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University. University Club (1925-)
Contents List
- Series I: Board of Directors, Minutes, and History, 1929-1999
  - Board Minutes - History and Foundation, 1921-10-13-1932-01-29 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Board Minutes, 1932-02-08-1937-02-10 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Board Minutes, 1937-02-10-1940-12-12 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Board Minutes, 1940-1953 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Board Minutes, 1951-01-15-1965-06-07 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Meeting Minutes - Bond Burning, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Meeting Minutes and Correspondence, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Meeting Minutes I, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Meeting Minutes II, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Series II: Contracts, Certificates, and Constitution, 1925-1986
  - Certificate of Incorporation, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - University Club/Virginia Tech Agreements, 1926 1929 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Bond Contract, 1929 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Notice of Impending Dissolution, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Deed of Trust Note, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Club Type License, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1976-1985 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - University Club Presidents, 1925-1986 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - University Club Constitution (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - University Club History (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Series III: Administrative Correspondence, 1930-1991
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1930-1935 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Series IV: Account Books & Credit and Payment Books, 1926-1978
  - Account Book, 1926-1934 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Monthly Summary of Expenses and Operating Funds, 1931-1935 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Record of Payments, 1930-1943 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Account Book, 1936-1956 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Record of Payments, 1944-1957 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Account Book, 1974-1978 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Series V: Budget, 1986-1999
  - "Bearin' the Budget" Article (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Budget, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Budget, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Budget, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Budget, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Budget, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Budget, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Budget, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Budget, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Budget, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Budget, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Series VI: Financial Records, 1929-1999
  - Registration of Owners & Class A and Class B Bonds, 1929-1943 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Financial Statement, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Financial Statement, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Financial Statement, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Financial Correspondence and Forms, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Financial Statement, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Financial Correspondence and Forms, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Financial Correspondence and Forms, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Financial Statement of the University Club, 1980-1983 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Financial Correspondence and Forms, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Fundraising Correspondence I, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Fundraising Correspondence II, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Financial Correspondence and Forms, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Financial Correspondence and Forms, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - National Bank of Blacksburg Account, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Financial Correspondence and Forms, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Durham's Business Services Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Financial Correspondence and Forms, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Financial Correspondence and Forms, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Financial Correspondence and Forms, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Financial Services, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - IRS Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Financial Correspondence and Forms, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Financial Correspondence and Forms, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - CPA Correspondence, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Financial Correspondence and Forms I, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Financial Correspondence and Forms II, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Financial Reports, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Financial Correspondence and Forms, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Series VII: Taxes, 1989-1999
  - CPA Correspondence, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - IRS Correspondence, 1989 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Tax Records, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Tax Records (1999) (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Series VIII: Workbooks, 1952-1957
  - V.P.I. University Club Workbook I, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - V.P.I. University Club Workbook II, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - V.P.I. University Club Workbook III, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - V.P.I. University Club Workbook I, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - V.P.I. University Club Workbook II, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - V.P.I. University Club Workbook I, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - V.P.I. University Club Workbook II, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - V.P.I. University Club Workbook I, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - V.P.I. University Club Workbook II, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - V.P.I. University Club President's File and Workbook I, 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - V.P.I. University Club President's File and Workbook II, 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - V.P.I. University Club President's File and Workbook III, 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Series IX: Management, 1980-1999
  - Manager's Manual (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Manager's Files, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Manager's Files, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Manager's Files, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Reports and Correspondence, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Committee Reports, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Manager's Files, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Presidents Reports and Correspondence, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Employment of Club Manager I, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Employment of Club Manager II, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Manager's Files, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - President's Reports and Correspondence, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Secretary Files, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Employment of Assistant Manager, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Long Range Planning Committee, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - President's Reports and Correspondence, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Assistant Manager, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Manager's Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Manager's Files, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - President's Reports and Correspondence, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Manager's Files, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - House Committee, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Manager's Files, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - President's Reports and Correspondence, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Election Correspondence, 1984-1988 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Executive Assistant Employment, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Manager's Files, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - House Committee, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Manager's Files, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - President's Reports and Correspondence, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Ballots, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Committees, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Treasurer's Correspondence, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Executive Director Employment Correspondence, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Manager's Files, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Attorney Correspondence Regarding Reception, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Executive Director Reports, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Assistant Manager Employment Correspondence, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Nominating Committee, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Assistant Manager Employment Correspondence, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Employment of Assistant Manager, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Election Correspondence, 1990-1997 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Payroll, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Election Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Employee Insurance, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Strategic Planning, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Financial Report and President's Letter, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Series X: Operations, 1984-1999
  - Policy and Operational Guidelines (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Operations Statements, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Operations Statements, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Operations Statements, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Insurance Correspondence, 1981-1987 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Operations Statements, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Operations Statements, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Insurance Audit, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Operations Statements, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Government Officials, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Operations Statements, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - University Club Assessment, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Worker's Compensation, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Operations Statements, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Worker's Compensation, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Worker's Compensation, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Series XI: Construction, 1927-1998
  - Blueprints and Construction Drawings (Folder 1)
  - University Club House, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Maintenance Correspondence, 1939-1963 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Bathroom Renovations, 1960 1981 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Basement Renovation, 1982-1986 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Construction Correspondence, 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Inventory, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Emerald Lounge, 1985-1987 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Renovations, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Renovations, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Maintenance, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Renovations, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Maintenance, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Maintenance, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Renovations, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Office, Hall, and Kitchen Renovation, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Renovations, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - EOAA Correspondence, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Ground Plan - Proposed University Club Developments (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Series XII: Community and Outreach, 1965-2000
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Comparative Study of University Clubs, Hofstra University, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - University Club - Alabama, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Virginia Tech Foundation, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Development Brochure, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Informational Brochure, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Newspaper Advertisement, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - The News Messenger article, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Development, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Informational Brochure, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Virginia Tech Foundation Account, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Development Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Greater Blacksburg Chamber of Commerce Correspondence, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - New River Current Article, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Virginia State Corporation Commission, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Montgomery Junior Assembly, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Virginia Tech Foundation, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Association of Faculty Clubs, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Featured Dining Publications, including The Grapevine, vol. 1, no. 1, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Hokie Hospitality, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - State Corporation Commission, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Virginia Tech Foundation, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Association of Faculty Clubs, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - State Cooperation Committee, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - State Cooperation Commission, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - University of Virginia Correspondence, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Radford University Newspaper, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Association of Faculty Clubs International, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - State Cooperation Commission, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - State Cooperation Commission, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Virginia Tech Foundation, Inc. Loan, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 86)
- Series XIII: Fundraising, 1983-1998
  - Fundraising, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Patron Plan, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Gifts Received, 1983-1985 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Patrons and Benefactors, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Fundraising, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Fundraising, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Fundraising, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 93)
- Series XIV: Personal Correspondence and Images, 1956 1984
  - Personal Correspondence, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Personnel Correspondence, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Personal Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Jordi Calvera (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Louis Shaven - Images of Club (Box 4, Folder 98)
- Series XV: Guest Books, 1982-1987
  - Guestbook II, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Guestbook, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Guestbook, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Guestbook I, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 102)
- Series XVI: Membership Operations, 1974-1999
  - Membership Roll, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Membership Roll, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Membership, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Membership, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Membership, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Membership, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Membership, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Membership, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Membership Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Membership Lists, 1985-1987 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Membership Committee, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Membership Letters, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Proposed Membership, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Annual Membership Meeting, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Membership Letters, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Membership Lists, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Membership Marketing, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Membership Letters, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Proposed Membership, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Membership Committee, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Membership Lists, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Proposed Membership, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Annual Membership Meeting, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Membership Lists, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Proposed Membership, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Membership Correspondence, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Membership Dues, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Membership Lists, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Proposed Membership, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Membership, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Membership Correspondence, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Membership Lists, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Proposed Membership, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Membership Committee, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Membership Dues, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Membership Lists, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Proposed Membership, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Membership, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Membership Dues, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Membership Lists, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Membership Lists, 1995 1997 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Membership Marketing, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Membership, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Membership Committee, 1996-1999 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Membership Renewal, 1996-1999 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Series XVII: Registers, 1984-1998
  - Club Registers I, 1984-1994 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Club Registers II, 1984-1994 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Club Registers, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Club Registers, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Club Registers, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Club Registers, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Club Registers, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Club Registers, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Club Registers, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Club Registers, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Club Registers, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Series XVIII: Residence and Use, 1957-1998
  - Club "Free Use" Policy (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Club Residence, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Club and Renters Operations, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Residents' Correspondence, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Club Residents, 1984-1987 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Residence Applications, 1985-1987 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - East Lounge Coffee Service, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Club Residence, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Resident Applications, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Club Usage Fees, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Cotillion, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Residents Correspondence, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Residents Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Smoking Policy, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Residents Correspondence, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Residents Correspondence, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Resident Issues and Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 9)